[GROANING, GRUNTING]
[BILLY]
What happened to you?
Why did you
suddenly snap?
You're right.
I snapped.
I was reminded of my dad.
I couldn't protect her from Dad.
But now, things are different.
- To freedom!
[MARJ] Real friends don't snitch.
I dare you to show
your messages and calls.
[CHARM] That's right.
[GROANS]
[ABI] Caloy! Why did you come straight
here? What if someone followed you?
How can you be sure
the taxi driver is telling the truth?
This taxi driver
is our best shot right now.
He's our only lead to the woman
who gave him the money.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I only told you to scare
the driver, right?
The driver.
You involved Jordan.
Now look what's happened.
How was I to know that Jordan
would also be there?
Did I know that, huh?
I didn't know, okay?
But here, look.
Now take a look at this.
Look, 'Bi!
LOVELIST'S JORDAN VALENTIN
INVOLVED IN ASSAULT.
We don't need trolls anymore.
The netizens themselves will
now shred him to pieces.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
- THIS IS DANGEROUS BEHAVIOR.
- TALK FIRST BEFORE FIGHTING.
Is that nice?
Caloy, you can't always
act like that, okay?
Things can't always be this way.
Especially now, Caloy!
Not now that I'm finally
getting close to my idol.
What if they find out that
we have a connection?
[CALOY] Why?
Are you close already?
Did you get inside their company already?
Not yet! How could that happen?
If Billy and Jordan go harder after you,
we're going to be in a tight spot!
That's my point.
That's why I can't do that.
My goodness, Caloy!
I can already imagine it.
Her friends would invite me out.
"Hey, Abi! Let's have a drink."
"Abi, I love you!"
"Cheers! Let's take a shot!"
"It's so fun hanging out with you, Abi!"
You know, like,
I'd be hanging out with her friends too!
I'd get invited to events.
I'd attend an awards night.
And then…
I want to get on stage,
accept an award, and give a speech.
"Thank you so much.
This is for you, Caloy."
And then everyone would applaud!
"Thank you. Thank you.
I love you all so much."
"You inspire me."
That's what I want, Caloy.
Don't worry.
Everything you said will happen.
I promise you that.
Besides, Jordan's already in jail.
- We're so close to--
- He was in jail.
Yes, he was.
But now, he's free.
His friend just posted
that he was released.
What?
H-how?
I have no idea. How would I know?
That's what I'm saying, Caloy.
We can't do things carelessly.
Do you know what'll happen
if we get caught?
You'll go back to prison again.
I'll finish the job. Wait a second.
Oh, calm down! Calm down.
- I'll go--
- Calm down!
I'll go to that man!
[CALOY RETCHING]
Go on. Go to him and vomit.
[GRUNTING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[VALERIE] Okay, fine!
It's…
[MUMBLING]
one, four, three, Jordan.
- What?
- Huh?
[JORDAN] What?
One, four, three, Jordan.
One, four, three, Jordan?
As in, "I love you, Jordan?"
It could also mean…
"I hate you, Jordan."
- Check it already.
- Really?
Well? Is it okay now?
I can't see anything.
Well, sorry then.
Okay, give me my phone back.
What is this?
- What is it?
- What, did you find any evidence?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
"5:00 p.m."?
"See you…
at Le Jardin Hotel?"
That's a five-star hotel.
You wouldn't…
even take me to a motel.
There are even cute emojis here!
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Love, let me explain--
[GASPS]
- You witch!
- [SCREAMING]
- Stop! No!
- Calm down!
You're going after my boyfriend
after being done with Jordan?!
- Billy, get her out of here!
- Stop! That's enough!
- Let him explain first!
- Go, Toni!
- That's enough!
- Wait, stop!
- Get that woman out of here!
- Stop! Enough!
- Wait, calm down first!
- Hey, stop texting my man!
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Yani.
What is the truth?
Why were you talking with Val?
Answer her!
It's…
This is why. Here.
[YANI GRUNTS]
I was asking her to help me
propose to you.
Why didn't you just say so right away?
Why would I?
It's a secret. A surprise.
Yani, it's just that out of everyone,
why did you ask Valerie for help?
[MARJ] We're right here.
Because she has a contact
at the Le Jardin Hotel.
They have a beautiful garden there, right?
An overlook with a view.
It's the perfect spot for a proposal.
I manage all of
their social media accounts,
so I told Yani that
I'd help him get a discount.
I'm sorry, Val.
We were mistaken.
We're very sorry.
I just wanted to help Yani.
And I wanted you girls
to know I'm on your side.
I just wanted to be friends with you,
even if we're not on the same level.
What?
Mm.
[WHISPERS] Easy.
[CHARM CLEARS THROAT]
Sorry.
I'm sorry too.
I messed up big time.
But, love…
why did your proposal
have to be so extravagant?
Well, you're always comparing me to Ralph.
Sometimes, you'd even say,
"Hey, Yani, did you know
Ralph took Charm to Boracay?"
"They had a vacation there."
"And did you know
they eat at Charcoal Haven?"
"They probably go there all the time
because it's so good."
"They also go to this place too.
It must be really nice--"
Sorry.
I never meant to make you feel…
That's why I did all this.
Just so I could make it up to you.
At least with the proposal,
I wanted you to see me as someone better.
I love you.
Even if you're just a struggling painter.
I love you even if you're sensitive.
I love you even if
you only take me to Dolomite Beach.
I love you even if we only eat
at a local beef stew joint.
You'll still love him
even if he doesn't propose
at Le Jardin Hotel?
What?
Well, now that it's out,
I think this is the perfect time.
Yans.
Did you prepare your proposal speech?
- Ready?
- Of course.
There you go.
What are we waiting for?
- Go, go, go!
- [CLAPPING]
Oh my God, girl!
- [YANI CLEARS THROAT]
- [JORDAN] Go, brother.
- This is it, girl.
- Go, go, go!
Love, may I have your hand?
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
You're the inspiration
behind all my dreams.
That's why I never give up.
I love you so much.
My muse…
Antonia Prieto.
Will you marry me?
Yes.
- [SQUEALING]
- [APPLAUSE]
- Oh my God!
- Yes!
- Congrats!
Yes!
- Congratulations!
- [ROBBIE] Go, Yani!
[APPLAUSE]
- [ROBBIE] Go Yani!
- [BLAIRE] When will our turn come?
- [BLAIRE] What about us?
- [YANI] That's true!
Thank you.
- I'm heading home.
- Hmm.
Home?
Can you even make it home?
I don't think you can.
Just stay here.
Sleep here tonight.
Thank you.
And I'm sorry.
Caloy, who is going to have our backs
if not each other?
Just friends?
Want me to add another bruise?
This time on the other side?
'Bi, I'm serious.
Hmm.
You've always been there for me.
If it weren't for you,
I probably wouldn't even be here.
- [BLADE SWISHES]
- [CALOY GRUNTS]
- Come on! Come on!
- [CALOY GRUNTING]
Bastards!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Help! Help! Hold on!
Take me to the hospital!
[GRUNTS] It hurts!
[HORN HONKING]
Sir, help me, please.
[CALOY GRUNTING]
What happened?
Oh, there's blood!
Sir? Hey! Are you okay? Hey!
Help! Help!
Oh! That looks pretty deep.
What, are you all deaf? Help!
Tricycle!
What happened to you?
Oh my God!
Get in!
To the nearest hospital, please!
Let's go, hurry!
Caloy, if I'd known
you'd just come from a fight,
I might not have helped you.
Just stay here.
Come on.
Lie down. Get some rest.
So I can head home too.
My parents disowned me.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
But you, someone I'm not even related to…
have always been by my side.
Caloy, we're the same, aren't we?
Our parents both abandoned us.
That's why we're all we've got.
So I hope you understand
why we need to keep our distance for now.
It's for our own good.
We have to be even more careful.
Anything for you, Bea.
What did you say?
Bea.
What did you say?!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUTTERS] Abi.
Hmm?
[LOUDER] Abi.
Get some rest.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THUDS]
[BILLY] Love gives second chances
to those who deserve it.
And these women are proof of that.
I believe that
love should only
be given to the right person.
And yes, there are still a lot
of good people out there.
That's why LoveList,
a matchmaking and dating app,
- is here for you.
- [PHONE CHIMES]
But we created not just an application,
but a community of women who work together
to help you find "the one."
Because I believe…
PAY BY MONTH'S END,
OR I'LL PADLOCK YOUR UNIT.
…that love is supposed to be
the most beautiful thing
that can happen to you.
As long as it is with the right one.
[PARTY GUESTS IN UNISON IN VIDEO]
At the right time!
[BILLY] And fun fact,
Toni and Charm…
[ABI] I can already imagine it.
Her friends would invite me out.
"Hey, Abi! Let's have a drink."
You know, like,
I'd be hanging out with her friends too!
I'd get invited to events.
I'd attend an awards night.
And then…
I want to get on stage, accept
an award, and give a speech.
[UTENSIL CLANKS]
You're already home late,
and this is what you bring me?
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
What kind of soup is this?
It's cold!
Then I'll just heat it up.
- [SLAMS]
- I've lost my appetite!
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
Are you hurt?
No.
Here. You can have it.
No, thanks.
I've lost my appetite too.
I'll reheat it.
Don't bother.
Don't bother. I got it.
I'll do it.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Daughter?
Sorry.
It's okay.
[PLATE CLINKS]
[CLATTERING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
- Hey.
- Hmm?
[PHONE CHIMES]
BIBOY'S FATHER
FILED ANOTHER COMPLAINT!
Please don't look at the comments.
If you want, we can take legal action
to stop the video from spreading further.
This is different.
- What is that?
- Mm.
Nothing. I got it.
Could you just get me
another drink, please?
You're driving, remember?
I'm perfectly fine.
- Look. Yes.
- Are you sure?
Thank you.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
What is going on?
- There you go again!
- What is it?
Is it your dad?
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Jordan is okay now.
But what we're not okay with
is how we still can't track down
the mastermind behind this.
WELCOME TO
THE PHILIPPINES!
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BUSY TONE]
[GIRL] Daddy!
Daddy!
[GIRL GUSHING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
There you go again.
You're making my problems
your responsibility.
Mm!
Why don't we talk about
how you ended up in jail?
- I'd rather not.
- Come on.
Go.
[BILLY CLEARS THROAT]
I'm sorry about that.
Are you really okay?
[FRIENDS] Kiss! Come on!
[CHEERING, CLAPPING]
- [BILLY CHUCKLES]
- [CHEERING]
- Whoo!
- [YANI] Let's go! Cheers!
- [FRIENDS] Cheers!
- [BOTTLES CLINK]
What about you?
Are you really okay?
Why do you keep asking me that?
You're like a broken record!
- I'm fine!
- Okay!
- Let's dance.
- Okay.
- Jordan wants to dance!
[CHEERING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC FADES]
It's turned red.
This'll definitely bruise by tomorrow.
So annoying.
[SIGHS]
I'm okay.
Hi, Ms. Billy.
Idol.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
There.
My newly-printed pictures.
I have another addition to my collection.
You're so beautiful here.
[LIGHT SWITCH CLICKS]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SQUEALS]
[SIGHS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE CHIMES]
Whoo! LFG!
- Whoo! Let's go!
- [PEOPLE CHEERING]
Congratulations for Yani and Toni!
- Whoo!
- Congrats!
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER,
CHEERING ON VIDEO]
Cheers!
Whoo!
[PEOPLE CHEERING ON VIDEO]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
- Whoo! Cheers!
- [CHEERING ON VIDEO]
- [TONI] Go Billy!
- [MARJ] Lower!
[MARJ] Go lower!
[CHANTING] Lower! Lower! Lower! Lower!
- Lower! Lower!
- [CHEERING]
[HEELS THUD]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
- [MUSIC FADES]
- [ENGINES REVVING]
Bye! Take care! [CHUCKLES]
- [CAR DOOR CLOSES]
- [ENGINE STARTS]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
Benilda? Sweetie?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[LINE DISCONNECTING]
Billy, why do you think
he suddenly called you?
After-- How many? Um…
More than ten years, right?
I don't know either.
Don't you think you should find out why?
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[PRECIOUS GROANS]
Billy…
I know it hurts and it's hard.
But maybe you should talk to him.
Not for his sake,
but to finally give yourself some peace.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE RINGING]
[LINE RINGING]
[LINE DISCONNECTING]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SIGHS]
Let's go.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Let me be
a mother to you just this once.
[BILLY] It's really hard
when you can't escape
the person who hurt you.
My father called last night.
You know you can
talk to me.
Anytime, okay?
Get used to calling me Abi.
Abi! Abi! Abi! Abi! Abi!
And we shouldn't be
seen together.
It'll be a big problem.
[YOUNG BILLY] Family
is never meant
to be split up.
Oliver's still
with you, right?
- What's wrong?
- Keep an eye on him. Please.
[BILLY] Oliver, no!
No!